Cinderella
Cinderella's Sister
Your room is still being constructed
so for a few days you will be sharing my room. Come this way.
Episode 2
Come and sit.
We have become like this.
Did you ever imagine this would happen when we met on the train?
Isn't it very very amazing?
I am sorry for not knowing you were my unni and not my age.
- But you look really young.
- Where can I wash?
I asked where I can shower?
Oh. There.
You need to change your clothes.
It's not in here.
This is for your stuff. I emptied it.
This is new. I bought it for you.
Are you always that talkative?
How did you know?
I am very talkative.
Unni, the pajamas.
Come out and then change.
The red toothbrush is yours and the blue is mine.
Put your hand under. When you put it under, the water comes out.
So because my mother was sick, saying the air here was good, my dad built the house here.
But the brewery was too far away to travel to
so he built the brewery right next to the house.
Since then, I've lived here.
How far did get before?
Ah, was it until I was seven?
Then the year changed and I was eight.
- What is it?
- Your life story is boring.I don't want to hear it.
Then, should I skip to when I was ten?
Starting when I was ten, it got really interesting.
Unni where are you going. I'll go with you.
Not if you don't want me to.
Why so sudden?
Hey, happy to see you.
I was getting bored.
Want to come and have a drink? When there isn't a guest, this annex is empty at night.
Come over here.
Is there something you want to sponge off of me?
Huh? Sponge off of you?
Why are you smiling? There's nothing you can sponge off me, so quit smiling.
Wait a sec. Theres something I have to ask you.
Do you smile when sponging off of someone?
That was the first time I heard that in my life.
It was laughable so I smiled, it was humorous so I smiled, I was joyful, so I smiled. It was nice so I smiled.
There weren't just one or two reasons to smile. Why of all things do you need to sponge off someone to smile?
- Is it laughable now?
- Huh?
Laughable? Humorous? Nice? Joyful? Why are you smiling now?
Am I smiling now?
She belittled me.
♫ In the colors is the rainbow that we see shining? (In Spanish}
♫ And that is why I love
♫ the great loves of many colors
Stand at attention. Bow.
Thank you.
Unni. I'm going to the store. Can if buy you anything?
While you are on your knees ...
"yo" (being polite, sarcastically) What should I call you? Just by your name?
Or if not, "Unni"?
Don't call me.
Hey, what is this? I was being nice because she is your sister.
What a loser.
C'mon!
What is he doing?
Bought a kiddie helmet...
Scared you? "What are you doing here?" Isn't that what you are going to say?
I mean the reason Hong Gi Tae came here ...
What's the score with the guy who shot this? Are you splitting it in half?
Or sixty- forty?
Oh. Seventy-thirty.
With things like this, you're quite smart.
If you put these things in the newspaper, there will be talk.
Chairman Hong Han Seok, your hidden youngest child Gi Hoon
was abused by his older brothers and father.
So your youngest is doing odd jobs for a local brewery.
They are perfect grist for grinding slowly in a rumor mill.
Smart brain, very smart brain.
Why? Isn't this enough? Are you smiling?
Nice to see you, Gi Tae. It's been a long time.
Hyung Gi Tae. If you have something to say, say it. Leave out the Hyung.
Is Hyung Gi Jeong also doing well?
You keep being a loser.
I mean leave out all the titles attached to family relationships when you talk.
I've never taken pictures like this.
It seems some bad man who needs money caught you.
Since you brought the pictures here, it seems you resolved the situation.
So there isn't a problem anymore.
Because I don't like calling you hyung,
Hong Gi Tae. You son of a bitch. There was no reason for you to hit me.
You told me stay away and I am.
You said to live quietly so I live here quietly.
I was lucky to meet a good man here and I am doing well here.
Don't appear in front of me and leave me alone. Got it?
Unni! Unni, let's go together.
Mom and dad are coming back from their honeymoon today. Let's go to the airport together.
Oppa Gi Hoon said he would give us a ride. Oh, there he is. Oppa!
Unni, hurry.
Unni!
Let's just go.
Why? I'm going to go together with Unni.
She's not the type who will ever listen to others.
Elders, please this way.
This is my grandfather's brother.
My father's cousin and his wife.
My father's second cousin's wife.
Please say something, aunt.
What are the four pillars of your destiny (i.e. birth year, month, day, and time)?
Excuse me?
That grandma used to be a shaman...
I mean, a spiritual person but now she is a pastor.
I guess her spirit and Jesus come to her alternately, very funny, right?
Right now, she seems to be getting intense vibes from you.
What a complicated family...
Why so many family relations and why force me to bow
to even second cousins twice removed of in-laws?
Aigoo, what a nasty lot I have...
In a house where I came to improve my lot, even if I fall backward...
Because of my swollen feet.
Let me see your feet.
This is a family with lots of relations, talks and incidents.
I am sorry for making your life harder.
Under the sky there were only Eun Jo and me, the two of us.
Are you done messaging them?
I have never been someone belonging to some family.
My Eun Jo... Except for her mom, she never had a father
or someone to call uncle or aunt.
It feels like the day when we finally
get to have a roof after living in a roofless house for a long time.
Thank you. I will do my best.
Thank you.
If you think you're going to regret this, tell me now.
Why? What is wrong?
People tell me that I seem ill-starred.
What use is my ravishing beauty when it will destroy my husband?
But what on earth are you talking about? Who says such nonsense?
Why do you think your father's second cousin's wife asked about my four pillars of destiny?
It is not like that. It's a useless worry.
She asks anybody about their four pillars.
Tell me now if you think you are going to regret this.
We haven't registered our marriage yet.
I feel sorry that you have such thoughts.
With me, you don't have to worry about such things.
Promise me, you will not be like this.
This foot hurts too.
Oh, okay.
Dad, Grandma Aunt says...
Oh! Are you okay?
When you enter elders' rooms,
giving a sign of your entering will be a polite thing to do, right?
Oh... I've never had to do this so...
I have no manners so...
What are you talking about, Aunt?
Until I say you can do it, delay the registration of the marriage.
She's not an ordinary one. It's not her.
- Ma'am-
- If we make a mistake, it'll be disastrous.
Goodness, I don't want to imagine it. My body is just-
It's written on her face. She'll completely take advantage of you, too.
So delay registering the marriage until I say so. Understand?
Don't be like that, Aunt.
What do you mean by don't be like that?
Whatever you don't know well and whatever you do know well, please don't say anything about either.
What do you know about that person?
That person and her daughter are now my family.
Don't say such hollow things about my family. Stop it now.
What do I do about what I can see with my own eyes.
Then, don't look.
Look here, Nephew. Look here.
They're my family now.
Stop saying such hollow things about my family now.
Look here, Nephew!
I was looking for you for ages.
It's not worth trying to walk away.
If you wait a bit, all the elders who are spending the night here like me will arrive.
There's somewhere good to hide. Should I fill you in?
It's nice to see everyone in the family come together.
Definitely.
Days like today are hard to come by.
Ah, of course.
Where is it?
Excuse me, excuse me. I've got a mom and a sister now!
Isn't my mom really pretty?
Applause! Applause!
Let's sit.
Father, have some.
Uncle! Have you not seen my Unni, Eun Joo?
I don't know.
Uncle! Then what about Gi Hoon?
I don't know!
It's chrysanthemum. Do you want to try a sip?
You should sit here and do it. Otherwise, you'll hurt your back.
Has he not seen my message?
Or, did I press the wrong number?
Does it make sense that none of my 10 text messages were delivered?
I think I need to change my carrier, right?
Unni, what carrier service do you use? Do your messages ever stop sending?
If not, should I change mine to be the same as yours?
Are you an idiot?
How can you so adamantly believe
that your texts can't just be ignored?
What religion is it that you're believing with all your might?
Are you giving your tithes on time?
Are you ignoring my messages?
Sis, how could he really do something like that?
If I sent 11 messages, shouldn't he reply to at least 1?
It can't be that he doesn't know Hangul (Korean Alphabet). Are the messages being swallowed?
Hey.
You easily send me more than 10 useless texts a day.
Did you see me responding?
Did you not know I didn't reply?
That's... because I see you all the time. At home, and at school...
Let's not talk.
Let's go together, Unni.
What are you doing?
It's Dong Soo.
Unni! Unni!
-Are you Dong Soo?
-Yeah.
You know her right?
Yeah.
-Why do you ignore her messages?
-Huh?
I find her whining really annoying. Whether you reply to her messages,
or if you tell her confidently that you don't like her, just muffle her. Understood?
♫ Even if you don't love me, I can give myself to you. ♫
♫ You, my love, that I've waited for so long. ♫
♫ Don't hesitate. The path we go down ♫
♫ will only be full of happiness. ♫
♫ All the times that were lonely, ♫
Right, today's lesson is over.
Thank you!
Huh?
Huh? It's Dong Soo.
♫ So that I can express my feelings to you. ♫
♫ I'll be there 1, I'll be there two. I'll only love you. ♫
♫ If I'm with you,  ♫
Hyo Seon's here.
Why? Why did you come crying, why?
I got a message from Dong Soo.
I'm back.
You came?
Unni, thank you.
Thanks to you, I got a message from Dong Soo.
A response came saying to never message him again.
Don't cry, my child. It's okay, it's okay.
Don't cry, don't cry.
Oh gosh, don't cry. My world, don't cry.
Are you studying?
Can you come out for a moment?
I'm fine.
Today...
Yesterday, I met your homeroom teacher.
I heard you're really good at studying.
A bit.
Since you didn't get to attend school in the beginning,
it must not be easy for you to catch up.
You must be smart.
I'm smart.
Besides studying, is there anything else you want to try?
Do you want me to send you to a dance academy like Hyo Seon?
No.
Then, what about learning piano or violin?
I don't want to.
Or just give it to me in cash.
What do you want to be in the future? What's your dream?
What do you have to say to me?
If you need something, ask me.
If you make plans for your future,
and you need some kind of help, tell me.
I will help you to the best of my ability.
It's okay for you to lean on me.
At your age, you must sleep well. Sleep early.
If you want to factor 2x cubed plus 54, you need to find the common denominator.
Then, you'll get 2x cube plus 27,
27 is 3 to the 3rd power, right?
Alright then. Someone should come out and try to solve this problem. Who's first place in Math in this class?
Song Eun Jo is!
Ah, really? Song Eun Jo? Can you come out and solve it?
Song Eun Jo?
I don't want to.
What?
I said I don't want to.
You're the best, Unni.
Excuse me. Where is he?
I'm here! (Because Korean doesn't have a third person pronoun, she just used an honorific form of "is")
I mean Hyo Seon's Father.
Over there in the office.
You need to greet elders first. Don't just come right out and get to the point.
Your rude behavior and bad attitude...
Ah, really.
I'm fine with everything else, but I get nervous with math.
Can I get a tutor?
Not some hot head, but someone kind of expensive.
A math tutor? But I heard your math score was high.
I memorized everything. I memorized all the questions and answers.
I have no foundation.
You memorized math?
You told me to tell you if I needed something.
What about learning language and science together as well?
I'm good at those subjects. I'm probably the best at school.
It's not great to use terms like 'hot head'.
In front of elders, you say "I" formally.
I know a skilled math tutor who can teach you things like this along with math.
When do you want to start?
Unni.
Unni!
If you keep acting like this, I'm going to get tired too.
I'm just saying.
Oh, you're here.
Should we start?
I asked him to get me a skilled teacher.
Then he chose correctly.
Oppa Gi Hoon goes to a really good university.
He's just on leave of absense right now. He's super smart.
Thanks. Sit properly.
I really don't want to.
Goo Hyo Seon.
I've started to get tutoring. How about you?
I have to go to the academy.
Right now? You're going to the academy right now?
Yep, right now.
Play with me a bit more.
You just take out the 7 and factor it.
Can you explain to me what factoring is?
Hurry up and explain.
Are you like this because you think I don't know, or is it because you don't know?
I don't know.
You learn this in middle school.
Do I have to tell you again that I attended school sparingly?
Okay, then factoring...
- What is it?
- Call me "Teacher".
And don't say "try and explain it", but say "please explain it to me" or "please teach me".
Hurry up and try it. Quickly.
It's not that I suddenly have respect for you, Teacher.
It seems you're really good at teaching...
No, it seems you're extremely good at teaching.
And asking to have my teacher switched is a nuisance. I also don't have much time...
Because I don't have much time, I don't want to waste it.
Please explain to me what factoring is. (Speaking very formally)
The tone of your voice bugs me a lot, but still, I think this is a big change.
But... what do you mean when you said you don't have much time?
I'm asking you to help me when you can. Why do you have so much to say? (Speaking informally)
I'm saying I don't know if I can stay in this house or continue to attend school for long!
I don't know when I'll get kicked out or have to run away,
so I'm saying I want to do this when I still have the chance.
What? Unni, what's wrong?
Oppa, what's wrong? What happened?
It's Hyo Seon...
Can I come in?
Come in.
- Unni Eun Jo didn't come?
- Eun Jo?
While studying, she suddenly left.
- What about Gi Hoon?
- He went out to find her, but both of them disappeared.
Really?
Look around some more. I'll go out to look too soon.
Why?
It's nothing.
Quickly tell me.
They must be like this because they're surprised.
Surprised?
They must wonder why their last names are different
even though we say they're siblings.
If we register our marriage, that's a solution...
You don't have to worry about those things here.
The boss here is a better person than anyone I've ever met.
I'm just a part-timer here...
But he's someone I want to try my best to serve.
You, who tries to scratch and run away like a stray cat on edge.
The fact that I tried hard to hold onto you isn't just because it was an errand I had to do.
I, too, felt like you.
I felt like you, but after living here, I became like me.
Don't I look cool right now?
I became cool here.
You'll be even cooler than me.
I'm sorry. I won't do that again.
I won't take away your study time.
Take the cosine of x...
If you use the log equation, you can solve these pretty simply.
Sin (x) squared + cos (x) squared = 1
tang(x) = sin(x) / cos (x).
When solving for x ...
If you just use these equations, tan(x) = sin(x)/cos(x)
then the sin(x) ...
I have to do homework too. I have something I don't know.
Hold on. Hold on.
Look at this, I'll demonstrate it for you.
x = 3. Got it? Next question.
- What is it?
- Explain this again.
Please.
♫ It must be you ♫
I cannot be without you ♫
Alright, I'll explain again, so listen well.
♫ Like this, for another day, month, or year ♫
♫ I don't mind, even if I am hurt ♫
♫ I don't mind, even if my heart breaks ♫
♫ Yes, if it's just you, it is enough ♫
♫ Because you are the only one I love ♫
- Oppa.
- What is it?
- Who am I?
- What?
I asked, who am I?
You're you. What do you mean who?
But... I feel a little strange.
Strange?
Hey part-timer! Your phone is vibrating over here!
Yes, Hyungnim.
- Oppa!
- What is it?
- Try saying "the moon is rectangular".
- Really.
- Try it.
- - The moon is rectangular. Alright.
- Hurry up, punk!
- Yes, Hyungnim!
Attend school well. Don't doze off in class.
School-Wide Math Competition
Hey. Don't you smell alcohol from somewhere?
Ah, so annoying.
The homeroom teacher must have drank again before coming to school.
- What's the occasion?
- The problem was sending Gi Tae.
He didn't pass on a word I told him to and came back.
- Is Boss Goo Dae Seong innocent?
- Yes.
Why does it have to be here of all places? Why did he have to come here?
Why can't he come here?
I didn't come all the way here to debate with you. Don't be insolent.
Leave here immediately.
While the Korean Economic Daily News published the its first quarter's eocnomic report, they are investigating you.
Since they're trash-like punks, they will ferret out trash.
My grandfather is already ill, because we're settling the inheritance,
our family is doing all kinds of things.
What does that have to do with me for you to tell me to leave?
- What did you say?
- Do I have an interest? Do I?
You said I didn't.
You even got my memorandum saying that because I don't have an interest, I won't ever ask for anything.
Does the memorandum not have any power?
Should I take one more picture?
Should I write it in blood?
Shut your mouth.
I need a more specific memorandum.
Write a memorandum that you'll give up the inheritance.
And leave here to go study in Europe or the United States, wherever.
What was your major again? Archeology? Journalism?
Anyway, once you graduate, whether you build something or analyze articles,
I'll make it so that you don't have any worries about being able to live and eat well.
I don't want to. Since I'm already being called trash, I might as well like as trash.
I want to get my inheritance and take a stand for my rights... I want to live like that.
Our father is healthy, right?
Gi Jeong... Hyungnim.
It's not uncommon for car accidents to happen on the mountain roads, so be careful on your way back.
That's okay. You're all I have.
That's right. I also have you.
Look at this. Isn't this okay?
Hey, you!
Among you all, is there anyone who does not know that my, Goo Hyo Seon's father,
and my unni's, Song Eun Jo's, mother have remarried?
- What did she say?
- What's she talking about?
Is there anyone who does not know why we're not Goo or Song?
If so, then come here now. Come here!
Goo Hyo Seon. Sit down.
Are you drunk?
Unni, who is it? Who made fun of you?
It was not the drunkard who was really drunk but Goo Hyo Seon, it was you?
Hyo Seon this girl, that smell...
Just tell me. Why won't you tell me?
Who was the one that made fun of you because of our different last names? Tell me.
Did you drink?
It was not alcohol... but pomace.
♫ Don't hesitate. The path we go down ♫
♫ will only be full of happiness ♫
We have this kind. How about this style?
It's not like that. She sticks ballpoint pens in her hair.
So is there something pretty instead of a ballpoint pen?
A ballpoint pen?
Ah, sometimes she sticks a pair of chopsticks in her hair.
Chopsticks? Ah, wait a moment.
♫ If I'm with you,  ♫
Office of Resident Registration
Husband Goo Dae Seong
Wife Song Kang Sook
I'm sorry to postpone something like this simple.
Let's take care of Eun Jo's paperwork quickly as well.
Honey. Wait a minute.
The Bathroom.
Husband: Goo Dae Seong.
Spouse: Song Kang Sook
My crappy life! My crappy God forsaken life.
I'm finally someone's wife at the age of 40.
I'm finally a family's daughter in law.
I'm finally someone's wife.
Song Kang Sook, congratulations you bitch.
Congratulations you crazy bitch!
Why don't you go in first?
I'll go to the kitchen to take a look before I go in.
Alright.
What would you have?
Am I a customer buying ramen at a convenience store?
Did I come to buy ramen?
Do I sound like someone who doesn't make sense?
I'm not sure what you're saying.
I mean, when you see me,
when you talk to me you stand up, not be sitting like that.
Take out all the dishes.
Dishes?
Why all the dishes?
How many sets are there when you take out all the dishes in this house?
Not sure...
Maybe around 100 or 200?
Fine.
Whether it's 100 or 200, take them all out.
Anyway, why all the dishes?
Take them all out and clean them.
If you don't want to feel my wrath, wipe them all.
Until they all shine. Do you understand?
So, you're saying...
That mom lied.
When you didn't say anything about it?
That mom lied to us.
That's right.
Lies. All lies.
Whether it's my mom or me. They are all lies.
Alright?
Hey! Song Eun Jo.
Eun Jo, come here.
Hyo Seon's here.
Unni.
Since our mom's here,
let's figure out the truth.
You guys are back.
Did you do well on your exam?
Let go of me.
Unni, I said let's ask Mom.
This little bitch.
Hyo Seon, are you okay?
You're not hurt?
My goodness.
♫ It must be you. I can't be without you. ♫
♫ Like this for another day, month or year ♫
♫ I don't mind even if I am hurt. ♫
Why did you hit her?
It was because of your reaction I noticed.
You don't know...
Listen!
It hurts. How could it possibly not hurt?
So what? So what if I hurt?
Even if you don't like me at all. I won't ask you to like me.
So don't force me to not like you.
He ran out saying that he's going to see your mom.
Kang Sook.
I'll write it. I'll forfeit my inheritance.
I almost believed for a while.
♫ Come to me. ♫